(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-05T23:21:50.988013",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ALERT
REPORT TO HEADQUARTERS IMMEDIATELY
SPECIAL MISSION ASSIGNED
MISSION
UNDERCOVER INVESTIGATION
TARGET
FIVE ESCAPED FUGITIVES
TEAM: JUSTICE
The Scarlet Queen ELIZABETH Rose Bloodflame
The Chaser GIGI Murin
The Artist with the God Eyes RAORA Panthera
The Ancient Automaton CECILIA Immergreen
don't, don't know me unpredictable
takin' you all below, takin' you all be-
don't, don't know me, irresistible
takin' you all below, below we go
they think they want it? (huh?)
they wanna ge - get down
They wanna get, get down
we take ' em down (down down)
We take 'em down, down, down
queendom in the borderline
run it, no surprise
you ain't gonna win, but you can try
told ya, you got no luck
end up in my lineup
listen, listen
run oh hide and scream out
Run or hide and scream out
already locked ya up
fool's games you always play
call me corrupt, won't hear anything
aiming my sight down right on your heart
throw in ' the keys out, shut down
Throwing the keys out, shut down
i ～
I...
love it, the forbidden (justice, just like that)
you 're never forgiven (justice, get get that)
You're never forgiven (justice, get get that)
not one to just forget
we got ' em
We got 'em
the higher i rise
down further you dive
stand in ' on the
Standing on the...
edge , don't know me , unpredictable , typical you
Edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical you
got nowhere to go
show you somethin' real , my level no you'll never know
Show you something real, my level, no you'll never know
as above so below , you should know
As above, so below, you should know
dudurudurudu
( we got it ! )
(We got it!)
run in the light , oh my dio
Run in the light, oh my Dio
what 's wrong , what 's right ?
What's wrong, what's right?
rush in ' in a fantasy
Rushing in a fantasy
wannabe disease
sure that you won't ever make it out
eyes follow now
do it , do it
Do it, do it
new target locked on it now ( now )
New target locked on it now (now)
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just the start
Just us, Justice!
We rise... We ride
Get down, get da-ra-da
Like it like that? Run it like that
Get down, get down, down, down, hey
Takin' me up, up, up, let's go
Goin' above, go below
Told ya, you already know
Don't ya, they know it
Run in the light, oh, my dio
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh, my dio
Come take a bite (Never ending, endless sky)
Love it, the forbidden
You're never forgiven
Not one to just forget
We rise... We ride, ride, ride
Standing on the...
Edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical, you
Got nowhere to go, show you somethin' real
My level no you'll never know, as above so
Below, you should know
Just a little unpredictable, beautiful
Just the start, let's get it, let's get 'em baby
Go, next level, almost criminal, as above so
It goes below
Yeah! Whoo!
Hello, everyone!
Hello! Hello! Ciao!
At last, we are in 3D, and we've gotten to perform Above Below!
We did it! Yeah!
We did! Our first performance, that was so awesome!
If you really liked the song from it, remember we have a hashtag #Justice3D!
Post it on social media, we'd love to see them! Yeah!
Huzzah! Now that we're finally in 3D, girls...
...don't you want to do an introduction, but full energy with a pose?
Full pose! Full poses? We have those! Full poses, ha, alright, okay.
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue...
...also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, the leader of Justice...
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame. Lovely to see you, to see you, lovely!
Whoo! So cool!
Gigi Murin, everyone! Keep that herder away from me...
Oh my god, look at her dance! Cecilia, be careful! Yeah, she's sporty!
...from Hololive Justice! First show of official Hololive English channel!
It really is. Hi everyone, it's me, ancient automaton from Hololive English Justice...
...CC, twirling, yay! CC! And then of course we have our...
Raora!
Ciao everyone! This is Raora Panthera from Hololive English Justice! Big cat means big trouble!
Yay! And everyone, take a look at where we are now!
Tadah! Whoa, so spacious! Touch grass, guys! Touch grass! Grass touched!
It feels so good, I'm so excited!
I guess I got to... take off my skirt.
What?! Look away! Look away! Oh my gosh, she's naked, okay...
It's not... naked! This is a got-cha, very very normal pants.
I see, I see, understandable. All right, that was wrong. That felt wrong.
Well, maybe you shouldn't have done it. Can I sit?
Can I sit also? Yes, it's very comfortable, okay.
HR? HR? Calling HR!
Liz! Liz, Liz! What is happening now?
They're fighting again. Whoa, as usual.
Stop fighting! Get on your places and shut up!
So guys, what's... what's... what's the plan for today? Do we... How about we, how about we...
I suggest ice cream! Ice cream? How about we get some ice cream?
Liz, ice cream? Well, it's our 3D debut, so I think it'd be nice to do something fun of course.
Ice cream! Ice cream is fun! Anyway, but I think...
We should play a game. Maybe a game?
A game?
And then whoever wins gets ice cream?
Ice cream!
ATTEEEEEEEEEENTION!
What? Wait.
Up and at 'em, maggots! It's time to get to work!
No slacking off while I, Sergeant Smokey, am busting my scales off for you!
Hey! Long time no see! How are you doing?
“Heeey”?! GET IT TOGETHER!!!
Now line up and stand at attention, peabrains!!
Ah, okay, calm down, dears.
Let's just do as Smokey says. It's his first big appearance.
But he seems pretty fired up.
Okay, I will do it for you, Liz.
All right, let's go. Huddle up!
Only for Liz!
Hey, Smokey.
Enough talking! Do I make myself clear!?
Sir, yes, sir!
I can't hear you!
Show me your war face!
Headquarters tells me you've been getting sloppy, so I'm here to set things straight!
Sloppy?!
I've got a few brutal challenges lined up to whip your sorry hides into shape!
What is that? Wow! Has that always been there?
Yeah, has that always been there?
Let's go look! Let's go look!
Oh, the keyboard! Wow!
Alright, read the rules!
Here we are. Let's see what it says: Think Fast, Move Faster!
Rule 1: This is a training exercise for both your brain and your body.
Rule 2: Use the giant keyboard to quickly input the answer to the question shown on the projector.
Rule 3: The trial consists of 10 questions per person. If you're stuck, you can skip and answer it later.
Rule 4: Correct answers with more letters will get higher points. Ooh!
As per my last email.
Rule 5: Let's see who can rack up the most points in 90 seconds!
90 seconds?! Ninety?!
No whining! Cecilia, you go first! Get in there!
Okay, I'll go first!
Get out of my way! Get out of my way! Get out of my way!
Cecilia, it's up to you.
Watch this, guys. Don't worry, I got this.
Are you really ready?
How ready are you? Are you really, really ready?
Wait, I gotta practice first.
All right, let's get started. You only have 90 seconds.
Okay, I'm ready, I'm ready.
Three! Two! One! Go!
What is Gigi's last name?
M-U-R... I know! U!
...I-N! You're in!
Enter!
One of Raora's goals as an idol is to publish an...?
Skip!
No, don't skip!
Elizabeth is from Great... Where am I from?!
E-X-A-R...
...D-I-A! You have one minute!
Hey, nice one!
Who wrote the play Romeo and Juliet? Answer with the full name.
Full name? Five points! Five points!
You can do it! Full name!
What's his first name? W-I-L-L-I-A-M!
W-I-L-L-I-A-M!
Come on! H-A-K-E-S-P-E-A-R-E!
This is so difficult! S-H-A-K-E...
William Shake... almost there! You're almost there! You got this!
...S-P-E-A-R-E! Do I press enter? I don't know!
Wow, that was a difficult one!
How many hearts does a fish typically have? Oh.
I don't know.
You can't say that word!
O-N-E! Enter!
You have five seconds left! Quick!
Granny Smith and Fuji are types of which fruit? Apple!
A-P-P-L-E!
Ah! Nice try! Nice try!
Okay, that's the only exercise I'm gonna do for today.
How many points did I get?
Let me calculate in my brain... go-ji-go-ji-go...
Nine points! Yay!
Wow, that's a pretty good score!
To start on! A good start.
Next challenger, MOVE IT!!
I guess I'll have a go...
We're gonna let her show you who's the boss. I'll tap in.
We're all... Oh, we're...
Are you gonna leave her like this?
Yeah!
You can do it!
Alright. I, the leader of Justice, shall go next.
Let's get started. Liz, are you ready?
Yes, count me in.
Three, two, one, go!
Alright, one of Raora's nicknames is "Big..."
You know! You know! You know!
C-A-T! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Enter!
Finally, someone who knows my question.
Alright, Cecilia likes to drink...
T-E-A!
She likes to drink coffee! No, no, no!
Gigi's fans are called...
Wait, what is that? That's a lot. G-R-E... Uh-oh.
M... That's a long... Oh, that's a long word. That's a lot.
L-I-N-G-S. Oh!
Oh!
Ah, trick question! It's Gremurins. That's her name!
Wait, really? Yeah, because...
Who painted the Mona Lisa? Next question!
What do you call a group of lions?
Who? Oh...
P-R...
I-D...
E.
Enter! Go, go, go!
Nice! That's correct!
Next. Which country is famous for inventing pizza?
Eh? I know this! Roman Empire? Roman Empire. I got...
Italy. Oh, I don't think this is...
I-T-A-L-Y. Enter!
I think it's the Roman Empire. Roman Empire.
What is the fear of confined spaces called? What is that? Does it exist?
I'm scared. Next!
Ah, I don't think I have enough time anyway. We will go...
Oh, it's done! Time's up!
Of course. Yes, of course.
How do you feel? How do you feel? Are you tired?
What's my score? What's my score, guys?
I think your score is being calculated.
What's my score? In my brain. In my brain, a brain.
Yes, good, good. Go, go. And carry the one. It was four.
You got four points.
Four points? What the freak?!
Oh, wait, don't feel bad. You did really well.
And the energy is fine.
No, it's because they tricked you with Gremurins.
Smokey: Cat girl! Let me see your typing paws!
Okay, I go, I go, I go.
You got this, Raora! Go, Raora!
Let's get started. Okay.
Three, two, one, go!
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest?
Don't look, don't look! Don't look at her.
Don't look! Don't look!
U... Y... You... You...
Oh, no, it's E!
B-L-U-E.
Enter! Blue!
Yay!
What is the name of Gigi's mascot?
Wait, again? Oh, no.
Gigi's mascot? Mascot!
P-O-P-O. Enter!
Yay! What is Cecilia's last name?
I-M-M-E-R... Go, go, go!
E-R...
Alright, qwerty. What's a qwerty keyboard?
G-R-E-E-N.
Wait, Raora... Second one. Go, go, go! Enter!
Yay!
Okay. Okay. Skip, too many words. Skip it, skip it.
How many legs do insects have?
Skip!
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon? Oh, oh, oh!
Skip, skip! I don't know any... Is this a walk?
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth?
Skip, skip, skip, skip!
It's too long, she doesn't want to spell them.
What is the highest female vocal range called?
Oh, oh, oh, you got this one!
S-O-P-R-A-N-O. I don't know any of these!
Good job! We're so proud! I'm sorry.
Smokey: Gigi, score! Okay.
Calculating, calculating.
Is it ten, right? Is it ten, right? Twenty? Twenty?
It was four.
Why are you sad?
Why are you sad, Gigi? You tied with me. I got a really...
Why are you so sad? Don't you think Liz did really well?
Yeah, don't you think I did well?
I, I, I think there is a miscalculation here.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Okay, okay. Next one, next one. Okay.
Oh, I guess it is me! Okay.
What if they are really hard questions? I'm scared.
You shouldn't be scared. I'm scared of really hard questions.
You can do this!
Okay, are you ready, Gigi? I'm ready!
Okay, let's get started. Three, two, one, start!
Which flower best represents Elizabeth?
Rose! Skip! What? No, wait, wait, wait! Keep it!
Uh, no, it's got it. Stop you!
I, N, Enter!
WIN! Yes!
C, H,
A,
T, T,
I, N,
Enter!
Ah... Okay.
Come on, I, S, A, A,
C, N,
E, W, T, O,
N, Enter!
He got it. Okay, okay, okay.
This feels way shorter than the real game.
Only one point. Skip, only one point!
What the...
Oh, you got this, you got this. Six, six, six!
I don't care.
I don't care. Skip, I don't care.
Eh... Skip, I don't care.
Think about it!
Oh no! Gigi! Come on! Come on!
Is it gas or air?
Oxygen! I think it's gas.
Oh... You got this, you got this!
X, Y, G,
E, N, Enter!
No! Woo!
Okay, okay, okay. Isaac Newton versus William Shakespeare, and they gave us the same amount of points?
That's not... That's not...
That's unfair. Smokey's doing... Smokey?
Yeah, I think it's unfair to play a game where we need to read.
That's not... Well, anyways, who's the winner?
Do you want to know your score? What's my score?
Want to know, Gigi?
What is it?
It's 10 points!
Good job! Good job, Gigi!
This is why you are a member of Justice!
Yes, that's why.
Hmph... Looks like you maggots still need some serious training...
Alright, time for the second trial, you knuckleheads. I got some special training gear for you!
What? What? What is... Oh, I was just chilling.
Oh! Don't hit me! Don't hit me! Abuse! What is this?
Ah, yes, we are going to have a duel.
What?
Gigi! Rules!!
Rule one of Dizzy Combat: Split into 2 groups!
Split into 2 groups.
And then, one member on each team is blindfolded.
And we have to spin 5 times. Spin to win!
Spin to win.
And after you spin 5 times, you'll face off against each other...
...in an epic sword battle! To the death?
To the death? We should do it to the death.
Yes, to the death.
And the teammate that is not blindfolded must guide...
...the other player to hit them. It's like a co-op game.
Guide the other person. A little co-op game, okay, okay.
First, before you pick a team, the points for each target:
Head: 5 points. Head, okay, yes.
Each arm: 2 points. Two points.
Each knee: 2 points each. Okay, that makes sense. Got it.
Elizabeth! Gigi! Time for you dirtbags to beat the snot out of each other!
Ah, yes! Huzzah! All right, Gigi, let's put on our blindfolds!
All right. Blindfolds, blindfolds.
Am I supposed to do... Hey, hey, hey! I got it, I got it, I got it.
Okay, you ready? All right. Okay, ready.
Am I in? Believe in yourself, I believe in myself.
Okay, no way, I'm going to guide you.
Yes, okay, guide us.
You strong, God eye. Okay, okay, and be careful.
I choose you, Gigi-mon!
When do we spin? We spin?
You can do it. You're the queen. You're the leader.
Grab, okay, ready?
And spin to win!
Okay, one, two, three,
four, five!
Five! Okay, both. Okay, okay, okay. That's it, that's it.
Oh! Right in front of you. A little bit, a little bit more on your...
Okay, well you have to walk like six steps. Three...
I have, I have the power! Elizabeth! Elizabeth on my side!
No, that's me, wait, wait, wait.
Don't worry. Wait, wait, left, left, left. Turn to the left, turn to the left. Attack, attack, attack!
No, no, no, there she is, there she is! Yes! You got... Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Okay, okay, roll away, roll away! Yes, yes, yes!
Go, go, Gigi, go! She's on the ground, she's on the ground!
She's on the ground. On your left, on your left, on your left. On your left.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, left!
Go, go, go, go!
Got you!
You almost got it.
No, my head's spinning! My head's spinning!
That's it, that's it!
That's three, that's three!
You're doing really well!
Oh, my head's spinning!
Okay, okay, you did it, you did it!
Did I do it? Did I do it?
Yeah, I think absolutely. I think you guys did it.
Well well well, looks like you numbnuts managed to scrape up 15 points in round 1.
15 points! Yay! 15 points!
15! 15 points!
Yay, 15!
Yeah, 15, not 50.
Alright, alright, gear up for Round 2!
Okay, okay, okay, give us... the balloon!
Is she... got eyes? Is she cheating?
What? No, I am not! Turn around, turn around.
All right, let's put your blindfolds on. Okay, help me please.
All right, let's put your blindfold on. Perfect.
Is it on? Yes, it's on.
Okay, can you see anything?
No, okay, watch this. There you go.
Okay, I'm ready!
Let's play!
Took you buttercups long enough. Now square up!
All right. GG, count us down!
I'm gonna do a countdown!
Three!
Two!
One!
Spin! And swing, one!
And two! Two! And three!
Three! Four! And five!
Okay, left, Raora, left, left, left!
She's bent over, she's bent over!
Stop! That's the ground!
No, not that way! Go behind! Okay, go!
Follow my voice! Go! Go!
Where did she go? Where did she go? Don't follow me!
Raora, straight ahead, straight ahead, straight ahead!
Straight, straight! Keep going straight! Straight!
Get her! Get her! Low, low, low, go low, go low, go low.
Go low! Low, Raora! Low!
Forward, forward... stay where you are!
Okay, now, now, now, now, now!
Low! Low! Oh gosh, did I hit?
Okay, you gotta swing! Swing, swing!
Forward, straight, straight!
Okay, wait. Get her! Get her!
Raora, forward! You did it! Yay!
Oh my gosh! That was... that was something.
That was... that was...
Gigi, score!
15 points! Yay!
Woo! Yay!
Oh, that was... I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy.
I am... I am scared of the darkness.
It is... it is okay, you're still my pretty kitty.
Your third trial is behind that door. What's the password?!
Oh, really? I can open it. All together, all together.
It's... 8-0-0-8!
Open! Ooh, fancy!
Whoa! That's cool! Kakkoii! Yes!
Cool! Yay! Let's go, everyone! Huzzaah!
At attention, you dogs! It's time for your third trial!
Uh-oh. What? What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a second. No one said anything about a life-threatening...
...challenge!
I... I am...
I think it is okay. Don't worry about it.
You're not going to kill us, right?
Roara, rules!
Okay, so number one. Balance the blocks while stacking them according to the color order on the instructions!
There are 5 levels, and you earn the same number of points as the level you clear.
But watch out! Advancing to the next level is your call, but make a single mistake, and BOOM goes the bomb!
If you mess up the placement, then the bomb explodes, it's game over! So yeah, you lose, game over.
Alright, who's ready to get SMOKED?
Well, Gigi, do you want to go first? Die?
Yeah! I will take the first bomb.
I will die for justice! For justice!
Do it for Justice!
Gigi, do it for Justice!
Gigi, some of these are amazing! Look at you!
[Smokey: You got 10 seconds to survive levels 1 and 2, then 30 seconds for levels 3 through 5.]
He's gonna sacrifice for us.
Wait, that's so incredible.
Ten seconds...
Ten, that's nine more than one.
Nice, kind of.
You got this. We can count to ten for you.
Ten times one, guys.
Can... can you count? Ten!
You at home, can you count?
One, two...
No, no, no! There is no time!
Okay, okay, calm down. Let's start.
Gigi, ready? I'm ready!
Okay!
Three, two, one, go!
[Title: Level 1]
Oh, look at this. Yellow and orange...
It's red, yellow, purple.
Raora thought it was purple. I am the purple.
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay, easy, easy. Good job!
Go! Go! Go!
You good? You don't do that!
Oh, it scared you. Are you okay?
[Title: Level 2]
Oh, yellow, green, go!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, all of them.
Good, four seconds. No way, it's impossible!
Three seconds, two seconds...
Oh no! Uh-oh, uh-oh.
We survived! We got each other!
She always believed in you.
[Title: Level 3]
Go Gigi, go! Go Gigi, go!
Red! Hey, this one you will have to do like a thingy...
Yellow. Okay, okay, okay.
Purple, okay, okay.
She's doing it, that's good.
White. Whoa!
[Challenge: Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!!]
Oh, pose! That's... Oh! Wait!
All right, that's pretty good! Oh, for ten seconds.
You're gonna keep it. Keep it!
Six, five...
Four, three, two, one... defused!
Wow! Good job, Gigi!
Really good, really good.
Good job, good job!
[Title: Level 4]
Oh, that's difficult. Why did the ghost do that?!
We're doing great, doing great.
This is not shape of... No, it's fine. It's really good.
[Challenge: Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!]
One-one was a race horse, two-two was one too, one-one won one race, two-two won one too.
Oh, nice! She did it! Whoa! Nice one, Gigi.
Okay, okay, next.
[Title: Level 5]
What? What? What?! Holy moly!
Why did they put this one so far?!
20 seconds is a long time. You can do it.
You can make it.
Can I? What is this?
She's doing it, she's doing it!
She's doing really well.
I need to go! Go, Gigi, go!
Look at her go.
Ten... Nine, eight, seven...
They're not... Six, five, four, three, two, one...
[Math Problem: 7 x 7 - 7 x 1 x 2 = ?] What?!
No!
Ah! Oh, she died for justice!
Gigi! Are you okay, Gigi?
Oh! Gigi! Are you okay?
Yeah, she died! For justice! She's gone.
She died. Gigi, are you okay?
Gigi.
Don't worry, she's just being mean to you.
It's okay. You're gonna be fine.
Wah! Aahh! Stop, stop!
Oh my god. That's not fair! That's not fair!
How do you do math in two seconds?!
That's not fair! Quick math, quick math.
You did amazing though. Yeah, you did really good.
Died for justice. Yeah, you did really good. It's okay. You did...
Gigi... Gigi, what are you doing?
[Smokey: Smells like a barbecue in here... You got 10 points!] All right.
Ten?!
I didn't even count that high!
Ten times one, that's ten.
Wow, that's... Can you count? Okay.
Oh, who's next? Someone else is gonna get blown up, right?
[Smokey: That's enough, chatterboxes! You're up, Raora.]
No, I don't want to get blown up. Okay, okay.
Someone is gonna get burned like Gigi.
What?! But I already... Do it again.
She licked us up. Oh, Gigi is licking!
You got this. So proud of you.
I'm ready to defuse the bomb.
You got this. You got this, Raora.
Go, Raora!
First, level one.
Okay, and in three, two, one, go!
[Title: Level 1]
Light blue. Easy, easy. Raora, you got this.
Purple. Got this.
And... Yeah! Good job!
Easy, easy.
[Title: Level 2]
Whoa, that's a lot of colors.
Purple. That's...
Wait, what's next? Purple.
Almost there, green. Oh, oh!
Yeah! Woo!
I knew Smokey was nice. Yeah, nice colors.
[Title: Level 3] Red.
These colors. Whoa.
Okay.
We don't have a lot of time. Don't worry.
We have a lot of time!
You got this, you got this!
Okay.
Pose, pose!
You have to do a full-on...
Yeah, why not?
Too many for my leg.
You just do... do the pose.
You can do whatever pose you want!
What?! What?!
Okay.
Why are you trying to make her do those poses, huh? Huh?
Yeah! What's next? Yeah, very cute.
Purple! I'm in the way, I'm in the way.
Orange.
We can huddle.
Yah! It's up.
Really good.
No!
Wrong color.
Wait, that's the wrong color.
Oh, she got this, she got this!
How much wood would a wood...
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck...
...if a woodchuck could chuck wood?!
Yeah!
Purple.
Pink. Who we are when we're catching criminals?
Oh, yeah. So many colors.
That's a lot of colors.
Okay, that's a lot of colors.
Yellow, yellow... black, blue.
You're almost there! Almost did it.
Wait, dark blue, dark blue. Oh, no, it's red, red.
35 plus 6 is... 41!
Wow! She got it so quick!
I'm so good at...
Wow! Why is her math question so much shorter?
Big brain! Big brain!
She did it!
Good job, everyone.
Pet, pet, pet...
Raora scored 15 points. Not bad for a blockhead.
15!
Yay! Nice job!
Thanks!
Yatta! Yatta!
Who's ready to get lit up next?!
Okay.
I'm all fired up, I'm ready!
Stop fighting, okay?
Okay, okay, okay. You know what, shut up.
Let's count you down.
Three, two, one, go!
That's a traffic cone.
Go, CC, go! Go, go, go!
Wow, so high.
That's like a candy.
That's hard to balance, it's hard to balance. Okay, okay.
Okay, purple.
That's too many.
That's okay.
Purple, yellow.
White. You got it.
Got it, okay.
Oh, that looks so yummy.
Yeah, this looks like...
Green, yellow, red.
Nice blue.
I can't... I can't... I'm color blind!
Green! You got this.
Oh, what's your pose?
Pose, pose, left or right.
I'm so relaxed.
Namaste.
10 seconds...
Now breathe in. Hold it, hold it! Hold! Hold!
Breathe in.
Woo! All right.
Okay.
Red. You can do it, you can do it.
Red, orange, green, yellow.
Wait, black. Oh, you're bringing over every single color.
Is this strategy? The strategy?
Balance, balance. Okay, okay.
The big black bug bit the big black bear, but the big black bear bit the big black bug back.
Yay!
Okay, lip-to-lip, no stuttering. Big.
Go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That was really fast.
You got it, nice, nice, nice.
White, white, blue.
We win.
Wait, what?
I'm bleeding. Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, that's black. Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh! Oh my god!
It's so over.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, oh no! Colors! I'm color blind, color blind!
Ooh!
Wait, you can't see me, right?
I love zombies.
Did you look, did you look?
Open your eyes!
You gotta face your fears!
Nice and smokey... 10 points!
Oh, I got 10! Woo!
And can you... can you count? Can you count to...
Ten.
How many fingers am I holding up?
At least four.
At least, at least four. Well... Queen.
Leader of Justice.
Leader of Justice. Take on this challenge.
Ah!
"Let's go!" "Yes!" "It's time!" "Justice!"
Show you what I'm made of! Go star!
All right, all right.
Fast, okay.
"We need to get to the..." "All right."
I'm going to make it look easy some with...
All right. Oh, these blocks are quite far away.
Um...
"All right, let us put the..." "Bring it on!"
Bring it on! Bring it on!
"Yeah, yeah, yeah!" "Oh, yes! Yes!"
Are you ready, Liz? We're going to count down for you, okay?
Oh, I'm ready!
"All right, Level 1!" "Yes."
Three, two, one, start!
Oh, that's easy. Come on, come on, you got this.
"Okay, she got this, she got this." "She got this."
Oh, the blue ones are far away.
She got it, she got it, she got it! Yes!
Aha!
All right. Ooh.
Uh-oh, okay, okay, no, that was good.
The blue's...
No, that one's there. That one's there. Okay.
All right, yes!
Yeah!
Oh, that's... that's a pyramid.
That pink pyramid... got this.
I but tell tell you, and then you sell it.
Oh, she's going to get it. Wait, wait, wait, what? Go!
What's this? What's this? She got this, she got this!
She's got to move, she's got to move! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
All right. Now, pose to disarm the bomb.
Oh. Yeah.
These poses are not seeming fair.
"Yeah, this pose..." "Any cool pose."
Oh, show us your coolest pose.
Why do we get yoga and they just get to do whatever they want?
We get yoga and they get a photo shoot?
Gosh!
"Why is there..." "Got this."
She's got this, she's got this.
"And I think... got this." "Fast, that's our queen!"
All right. Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear, Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair, Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn't fuzzy, was he?
"Was he?" "Ooh."
All right, Level 4 is done.
Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear. Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy Wuzzy... I can't remember the rest.
Cats and boots, cats and boots, cat and boot...
Fuzzy Wuzzy, he's a bear, didn't see him anywhere.
Yeah, I'm the queen of justice, and... uh, what rhymes...
"That's just." "You know what rhymes with justice."
"Think about it." "Justice... Ice."
"Just ice." "Get me out of here." "Yeah, just ice."
Okay, okay, okay, difficult.
I need the lime one, and then, and then, I need the pink one and the blue one.
Wait, no, I don't need this blue one. Get it out of here!
Oh, the light blue, light blue, light blue. You got it, you got it!
I need this one, I need this one, and I need...
No! No! No! Everything's falling apart!
"No, it's not, it's not. It's not falling apart. No, you can do it, you can do it!" "Can I get it?"
No, get it... Hurry up, we're on the side!
Yes! Yes!
"What the freak?" "No!" "Get out of here, get out of here."
"I mean, yeah, that's fine. Well, whatever. It's, it's... I don't care." "Kick them, kick them. Get out of your area, kick them."
I don't want to do math anyway. It's fine. I don't want to do math anyway, it's fine, it's fine.
I got some math for you... 10 points!
10 points! Yeah!
"Huzzah!" "I think that's pretty good, I think that's pretty good."
Simmer down, buttercups! You still got the final trial!
Quizzes and tests! We don't want to do math anymore!
We just want to relax, Smokey.
Oh, I'm getting tired. Yeah.
Oh, well.
"Let's go." "Ice cream, ice cream." "Let's go, I want ice cream now, bye."
Wait, what the freak? Hey, hey! I'm the only one still burnt up! Hey, can I go...
Can I go shower real quick before the next, next game? Huh?
Hello? Oh.
[Now Loading...]
Taking you up low, taking you up, bee. Haha!
All right, all showered up. I don't smell like a cheeky chicken, well, burnt cheeky chicken anymore.
Oh, maybe they're hiding.
All right, I know a way to bring them out.
Justice... just like that!
Justice! Get, get, get, get!
You were hiding this whole time. Oh, goodness. Hello, pretty kitty!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll be okay, I'll be okay.
All right. Haaah!
It's time for the final trial, twerps!
Cecilia, rules!
Okay! / Yes, sir.
Humph. The final trial is Hammer of Justice! Whack-a-Gnome!
Gnome. / Whack-a-gnome. / Whack-a-gnome.
Okay, here are the rules. Number one.
Defeat the evil gnomes... / Evil? / Evil?!
...emerging from the wall by striking them with a giant hammer!
Number two. As we've all learned...
...not all gnomes are bad! Some are friendly, some are nice.
So be careful not to hit the good ones, and only hit the bad ones.
Only the bad ones. Okay, okay. / Bad ones.
And then, if you smash the bad gnomes, you get three points.
And if you hit the good gnomes, you get minus three points.
Okay, so we're supposed to hit the bad ones. / Right, okay.
How do we know? / No, no, we'll be able to tell. Okay, okay.
And then, be careful to aim carefully!
And then, at the end, how many points can you score...
...in 30 seconds? / 30 seconds?!
So, they come out of the holes, and then you have to hit them. And then, there's good gnomes and bad gnomes.
But wait, I can't tell. / Good gnomes and bad gnomes. Okay. / Are you a bad gnome? / I just hope I can tell.
Here's the bad dude you gotta feed to the worms!
Whoa! / Oh! / Sunglasses inside?!
Sunglasses means they're bad ones?
And this is the good one. No friendly fire!
Oh, that's the good one. / Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, so red hat, no sunglasses - good. / Not the sunglasses.
That's the good one. / No sunglasses. / No sunglasses, don't hit this one.
Whack-a-gnome. / Okay, okay.
Alright, put those muscles to work, big cat.
I got this one, guys! I got it! I got you!
Oh, there it is.
Oh, come on, pretty kitty. It can't weigh that much.
Ugh! / Go on, you can do it.
Believe in me, who believes in thee! Let my voice be your strength, pretty kitty!
Use your god eyes!
God eyes? Haaaaah! I can do it!
Haah! Oh! I'm scared!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ready to roll? / I am ready.
I have the power of justice and cute girls.
I can do it. / You got this! / I can do it!
All right, it's time to whack a gnome! Are you ready? / Yeah! I'm ready!
Three, two, one, start!
Thirty seconds! / Crazy! She's doing it!
That's the hammer of justice, that's her. / Look at her go!
Close to us! / Kill the gnome! Kill the gnome! Kill the gnome! / Kill the gnome!
I don't know how to feel about... / Oh god.
Help! Help! / No! / Kill them!
Oh gosh. / It did! It's disgusting! It's disgusting! / It is disgusting.
Why are there cucumbers? / Why is there a cucumber? / A cucumber?!
Hit the cucumber! / Kyaah! Aaaah! Oh!
Oh geez. / What was that? That was not a gnome. / Ugh.
That was a weird green gnome, huh? / Disgusting.
Oopsie daisy... I forgot to mention hitting cucumbers give you 5 points per hit.
Five?! / Five?! / She got a bit of those! / Yay! / Yay!
I feel like you should have said that earlier. / We got so many points then, probably.
Total scores will be tallied at the end of the game. Which one of you meatheads is next?! Move out!
Who's next? Who's next? Who's next? / Liz, I think it's your turn now. / Oh!
Well, okay then. Let me just, uh, take off my jacket. All right.
Flame off! Let's go! / So cool.
All right, let me go get the, the hammer over here.
Time to earn your title, 'leader'!
All right, are you ready, Liz? / I am ready. Okay. / Countdown.
Three, two, one, go!
Thirty seconds! / Crazy! She's doing it! / That's the hammer of justice, that's her. / Look at her go!
She's so fast! / Ah! Ugh!
That's a lot. That's a lot of them. / Get, get, get the bad ones.
Get the bad ones. / Oh, a cucumber!
Aah! / Cucumber!
Ten seconds, Liz! Ten seconds!
Five, four, three...
Kyaah! Aah! / Nice! / What the freak?!
Yay! / You did it! / I feel bad about hitting those gnomes. My granddad has gnomes in his garden.
You did amazing. / But like, they also eat... / No, they're usually quite nice.
Sympathy ain't gonna help you catch Advent! Gigi! Show no mercy. / Oh my god. All right, Gigi, are you ready?
Okay. / Are you ready for this little Gigi? / Oh, the gnomes.
Come over here and get the, the hammer over here. I left it over there. There we go. / I can do it.
I thought it was heavy.
She is built for this. She does this everyday.
Oh. Uh, I mean, it's, you know, not as heavy as the other one, so...
You can do this, Gigi! Go!
Come on, Gigi. Come on.
All right. Lift with your legs. Lift with your legs, all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Your claws! Your claws!
With my legs! With my legs! We're done, we're done.
My gloves! I'm stronger than this!
All right, Gigi. Break a leg, or break a gnome in this case. Thank you, Liz.
All right, here we go! Three, two, one, start!
Oh. Oh. No. Gigi, Gigi. Gigi, I don't think that's how...
Oh. No, that's the wrong color, Gigi. Gigi.
That's the... Gigi, that's the color... Take out the purple ones!
Just the purple ones! Just the purple ones!
I win! I win! I win! I win! I win! I win!
Oh, well, she got the cucumber. Oh, yeah. Yeah, maybe that counts.
Is it talking to her?
No, what I must do.
No, I know what I must do.
Gigi? What are you doing? Why are you looking at me like this, Gigi?
Gigi, no, Gigi. No, no, no, Gigi, Gigi, no, no, no! What are you doing? No, no, no!
Hey! Someone...
Why can't I hit her? Oh, she's so good!
Why can't I hit her?
Whoa. I should learn that. That seems like a good dodge move.
Ew!
Hey, what's wrong with the cucumber? Disgusting!
You must teach me that move sometime. I will do it.
Hey, when it jumps like that, it's... I don't know what happened. I just lost consciousness.
That cucumber has... That was really, that was really impressive. Thanks.
Button those lips! Cecilia! Get in there!
Okay, I'm ready! Avenge me. Oh wait, we need the hammer.
Let's cheer for Ceci, okay? Okay.
Here we go! It's time to whack a gnome!
All right. Three, two, one, go!
You know what, Smokey? You know what you are doing to us the entire time? Yeah, you're trying to make us play games.
But I'm not going to play your games! I'm not going to play your games! Because I do not discriminate!
We hit them all! I do not discriminate! She's on a rampage! She's hitting everything.
Cecilia! Cecilia! Oh, all right. Yeah.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Sorry. Sorry.
I've had enough. I've had enough, Smokey. You're pitting us against each other, but we will not play your games any longer.
Yeah! We'll happily play your games, sir.
Yeah, we'll happily play them. No, it's a joke, you know? Funny, you know?
We have humor too. Not just strength, but, uh... Are you okay?
Goin' AWOL, huh!? 0 points, you slug! Oh, well.
I don't want any more! You make us do sports the entire... Cecilia, it's okay. I'm sick of it!
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, there, there. Enough of you.
Take this! Take this! It's okay. I'll rock you. It's okay.
Why do you keep pulling us, Smokey? Don't cry. La, la, la, la, la. I'll sing you a lullaby.
He's quieted somehow. Did we escalate this?
Wait, we need to stop this. Stop, hey, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
We hit him! I'm sorry, Smokey.
We make sure that this is not going to happen again. We're sorry! We're sorry! We're sorry! No, no, no, we're sorry.
Who, who has the highest score?
Just tell us. Tell us, Smokey. Come on. Tell us, Smokey. Come on, end this pain.
After four trials, one of you clowns came out on top...
The winner is... Raora Panthera! You win, cupcake!
Yay! Thank you! Thank you! My pretty kitty!
Good job, good job, good job. Good kitty, good kitty. Yay!
You're indeed a great cat!
Zip it! It's time for our winner to make her little announcement.
A sweet little announcement.
We'll be performing the new song right now!
Right now!? Yay! Justices, are you ready?
Yeah! Woo! It's going to be so nice.
We've been practicing our singing and dancing really, really hard to perform for everyone today.
So make sure to watch our very first live performance!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm...
...infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I'll seek you out
Reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of my veins, feel my pulse, it's rising and igniting...
...fire!
Snuff it out!
Walking the line, on the edge...
...of becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade!
Ah, ah
Walking the line, fell so far...
...into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade!
Justice, it's just like that, I...
...don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass...
...is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out!
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash!
Renegade, I'll make 'em!
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash!
Renegade, I'll make 'em!
Bound by a vow, can I tread the waters lightly?
Never making a sound, incognito dio light the pathway
Burning 'em out, in the fallout I'll stand in the ashes
Fire!
Snuff it out!
Walking the line, on the edge...
...of becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade!
Ah, ah
Walking the line, fell so far...
...into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade!
Justice, it's just like that, I...
...don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass...
...is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm...
...infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
The light goes out!
イェーイ！やったー！
Yeah! We did it!
みんな！私たちのパフォーマンスはどうだった？ねえ？
Everyone! What did you think of our performance? Huh?
イェーイ！みんな『Renegade』たくさん配信で聴いてね！1位にしちゃおう！
Yeah! Make sure to stream Renegade! Let's get us to number one!
それからみんな、今日のレッスンの感想や...
And also guys, be sure to... remember, share your thoughts...
お気に入りの瞬間を...
...and favorite moments from today's training...
このハッシュタグでシェアしてね！
...and live performance with the hashtag...
「#Justice3D」！
#Justice3D!
「Justice 3D」！
Justice 3D!
あれ、あれ？
Uh oh, uh oh.
何の音？アラームが鳴ってる。
What's that? There's an alarm.
緊急事態かな？ちょっと見てみようよ。
Is it an emergency? Let's take a look.
よし、よし。みんなこっち来て、見てみよう。
Alright, alright. Everyone come over, let's take a look.
アビュード（Advent）！
Advent!
踊ってる！
They are dancing!
歌ってるよ！
And singing!
すごく可愛い！愛くるしいね！
They look so cute! So adorable!
こっちに手を振ってるよ！
They are waving at us!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
どう思う？ステージに行ったら捕まえられるかな？
What do you think? If we go to the stage, we can catch them?
もちろん！もちろん！
Of course! Of course!
あの子たちのエリアに行きたい！
We want to go to their arena!
Yes, yes.
Yes!
All you punks think about is standin' on stage! Go, get out of my face! And make sure you catch Advent!
We'll give them a taste of their own medicine, right guys?
Let's go!
Just like this, just like that!
Let's do this!
Here we go! Here we go! Go, go, go, go, go, go, get out of here!
Huzzah!
Where are they? I've been here for five hours now.
Five hours?
Huzzah!
Six hours maybe.
We did it, we're here!
You took so long!
You're so great! You're so pretty!
I had to take a shower, you know?
Shower? What for?
Cucumber-scented. That's me, yeah.
Wait, where are they?
They're gone.
Maybe because you guys are too slow!
What?!
Do you see them?
No.
Uh-huh, I see how it is.
Well, you know... silly.
Maybe we should perform the song we all worked so hard practicing.
Oh, that sounds like a good idea!
Crowd!
All right, let's get in positions, everyone!
In position! Okay, okay, okay!
One, two, three, four, let's go!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean,
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you.
手たたこう 手たたこう ほら一緒に
Clap our hands, clap our hands, come on, together!
Everybody clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky,
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it resounds.
手たたこう 手たたこう
Clap our hands, clap our hands.
光射す 僕たちの未来
Light shines upon our future.
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
All right, Justice!
波を揺かす Diving
Making waves, diving,
待っても意味ない Timing
There's no point in waiting, timing.
網の目魚みたいに Swimming swimming
Like a fish in a net, swimming, swimming.
引き寄せる Lightning
Drawing in the lightning.
まだ見えない Maybe
Still can't see it, maybe.
その先には何かあるの
Is there something beyond that?
まだ早いよ Sect
It's still too early, sect,
追い付くまで Shaking
Shaking until we catch up.
demo 虚しく待って Thinking thinking
But waiting in vain, thinking, thinking.
軽くスルー Changing
Lightly letting it slip by, changing,
飛び出すのさ Step-in
Leaping out, step in.
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ My dream
I'll show you I can seize it, my sparkling dream.
彼方の海まで Story
To the sea beyond, story,
繋ぐから
Because we'll connect it.
さあキミに ずっと見て欲しいから
Come on, because we want you to watch us forever!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean,
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you.
手たたこう 手たたこう
Clap our hands, clap our hands,
ほら一緒に
Come on, together!
Everybody clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky,
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it resounds.
手たたこう 手たたこう
Clap our hands, clap our hands.
光射す 僕たちの未来
Light shines upon our future.
今日は要らない Breaker
We don't need a breaker today,
リセット行こうぜ Breaking
Let's go reset, breaking.
何時でもいいでしょう 始の刻
Anytime is fine, the time to begin.
キミは何を Feeling
What are you feeling?
解き放って Sparkling
Release it, sparkling.
暗闇に手を連れて ハイパーウェイブ
Take my hand in the darkness, hyperwave!
光らせて Stage
Make the stage shine,
創るから
Because we'll create it.
さあキミに もっと見て欲しいから
Come on, because we want you to watch us even more!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean,
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you.
手たたこう 手たたこう
Clap our hands, clap our hands,
ほら一緒に
Come on, together!
Everybody clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky,
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it resounds.
手たたこう 手たたこう
Clap our hands, clap our hands.
重なる Wave 世界を揺らせ
Overlapping waves, shake the world!
One, two, three, four, five, six, do it!
終わりがあることくらい 当然 I know
Knowing that there is an end, of course I know.
でもまだまだ泳ぎ足りないの
But we still haven't swum enough yet!
Going crazy
あの日夢見た景色
The scenery we dreamed of that day.
次元混ざり合う すべて塗り替える
Dimensions blending together, rewriting everything!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands, to the other side of the ocean,
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it reaches you.
手たたこう 手たたこう
Clap our hands, clap our hands,
ほら一緒に
Come on, together!
Everybody clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Everybody clap your hands, to the other side of the sky,
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, hoping it resounds.
届きますように
May it reach across
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に everybody
C'mon now, everyone together
光射す
The light shining down
僕たちの未来
On our future
Just, sis, just like that!
Just, sis, get, get, get, get!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
Always striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Been smashing barriers left and right
That's our myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright
We've been together for what feels like an eternity
The times are changing, but we're ready for infinity
Yeah!
Our stories align
We're gonna go far when we combine
So look at the horizon and then look beyond
We'll marvel at the skies and the strength of our bond
We're making a vow to the smiling stars
A powerful moment that's all ours
The seasons change, but we keep shining
Now everybody sing!
Keep it going!
We're making our way to the next dimension
A million thrills in every direction
We'll give every mile our full attention
Breaking tension, breaking through
We won't miss!
With endless energy, stronger ties
We got this!
A perfect harmony we devise
We promise!
So clap along with me
Time to rise!
The future's right before our eyes
A new dimension of freedom that we've found
Yeah, we've made it
We're breaking out of the mold, no longer bound
We're unlimited
We're gonna spring to life and break the chains
Turn up the hype, can't be contained
We're shaking up the status quo
No time to stop, we're good to go!
The whole wide world is listening
So everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question, we'll break through!
Don't relent!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
It's advent!
It's awe-inspiring, going well
Represent!
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
Yeah! We did it! Awesome! Amazing job, today!
Yeah! We did it!
We did it! We did it! We conquered the trials and performed the song!
And what's more... what is it?!
Justice...
...just, sis, just like that!
Just, sis, get, get, get, get, get!
But wait, we're not done yet! We have not one...
...but two big announcements! Yeah!
First up, drum roll, please!
Introducing the official Justice 3D Showcase Celebration Merch!
All right, everyone! Get into your merch positions!
Oh, merch positions! Right! Okay!
Okay! First...
...we have Sergeant Smokey's design Multi-Case!
It's a multi-case! And if you also want to be Sergeant Smokey and boss us around...
And this is for you.
A handy item to store your favorite goodies!
On the left side, you can keep button
badges and keychains.
The right side fits...
...smaller acrylic stands or postcards!
Yay! Woohoo!
There's also a hook on the back
to attach even more keychains.
We'll be so happy if you show off
our merch at events, please.
Thank you so much!
Yay!
All right, Raora, your turn. Next.
My turn. Hmm...
All right, everyone!
Next, next one is the
life-sized 3D acrylic stand!
Life-size?! Woah!
Life-size, baby!
No, no, no, not life-size, no!
Wait, life-size?!
I didn't even notice.
I didn't even notice after I repeated it.
I was like, "Wait, life-size?"
Big size! It means big acrylic!
Ah, okay, okay, that makes sense.
Big acrylic!
Huge size.
In fact, Justice is coming to life
as 3D acrylic stands!
Everyone loves acrylic stands, right?
Yes! I love them!
Whether you have a room dedicated to
acrylic stands or just starting your collection...
...you are going to need all of Justice, okay?
Get them all!
All of them!
Woohoo! Next one!
Oh, it's me!
Okay! Woohoo!
And as we all mentioned during our 3D showcases...
...we each have our own merch too! Oh, la la!
All right, then, I will start!
Hahaha!
This right here...
...is the Paper Knife & Acrylic Stand.
It's a lovely...
...set inspired by the design
of my sword, Thorn! Yeah!
Thorn!
This paper knife can actually be displayed
by resting it on the acrylic stand.
It's so cool!
You all get your own Thorn!
Yay!
Little baby Thorn!
So cute!
Oh gosh, I can't... I can't... It's so cool!
Gigi, your go, your go, your go!
Hahaha!
And now...
...a Hand In Cushion for Gigi!
Do you remember seeing it?
Sadly, there is no Otomo-san to show you
how soft and fluffy it is.
But it is very fluffy, and it's made
from a very squishy material.
You'll never want to stop squeezing it!
I'm gonna squeeze it! She's gonna squeeze it!
And it's Otomo! Yeah!
Cecilia!
Woah!
Check this out!
It's Otomo Pouch & Socks set!
And if you wear the socks, Monday, Tuesday,
every day of the week, seven pairs of socks!
And then you'll have your little pouch,
the little Otomo pouch to put your socks in!
Yeah!
Um, it's really cute. You can put anything
in it, of course, not only socks.
But yeah, I really like it. It's a little Otomo,
and it reminds me of the Otomo pouch I made once.
I like it a lot! Yay!
Nice, nice!
Okay, Raora.
You can put your toes in your Otomo socks!
Hahaha! My turn!
And this is Raora's Pencil Case & Keychain set!
It's me wearing a Cecitino costume, and, ah...
...it's so cute!
You like it? Yeah!
I'll be so happy if you fill it
with lots of stationery...
...and use it at school, or in the office,
or really anywhere you want!
And the keychain can be
attached to the pencil case...
...so you can clip it to your bag
or anything you like!
Very cute.
Cute! Woohoo! Mascot Cecitino!
Yeah!
Everything is really cute!
I'm super excited for you guys to...
...I'm very excited to see all of Justice's merch, and...
...if you want to know: "When can we purchase some?"
Well, they will all be available to purchase
right after this stream!
So make sure to purchase them ASAP!
And that's our merch announcement!
Yeah! Wow!
That's the first one, and...
And as CC just mentioned,
there is one more announcement.
And you all know Justice will be performing
live for the very first time...
...at the Hololive English 3rd Concert!
Woohoo! Oh my god!
Taking place at the Radio City
Music Hall in New York...
...on August 23rd and 24th PDT!
And...
...right after this stream...
...we will be redirecting you into
the music video of "All for One"...
...song's music video!
Yeah, Justice also is in there, of course...
...and maybe you'll see us doing some stuff!
Who knows? You'll have to wait.
We'll be moving and grooving!
Maybe! So make sure to stay tuned,
it's going to be very, very soon!
Gosh! All right, everyone... Oh gosh!
It's getting a little sad...
...but it's almost time to say goodbye.
But before we go, let's each share our thoughts and thank all our fans for their support.
Uh, Gigi, you go first.
Me? Me? Okay!
Grems! Thank you so much for supporting us all this time!
And can you believe it's been a little over a week now?
And so many more years with Just Chats, Justice, and Grems! Yay!
Hello! Thank you so much!
Gosh, Rosarians, give me a mighty huzzah!
We did it! Oh my gosh, thank you so much for joining all of us on our adventure here...
...at Holo. I can't- I can't believe it. Oh my gosh, we're 3D now!
And we're going to be in a concert, and... everything's happening!
Like, all our dreams are coming... coming true, and it's all thanks to you guys! Thank you so so much!
Onwards and upwards! Huzzah!
Thank you very much. Thank you so much, everyone. Thank you, Just Chats, thank you too, thank you everyone.
Thank you, Justice, of course. It's been a lot of fun. We worked very hard...
...and I'm so excited and happy that you all got to see it finally.
And we're also really excited to be in the EN 3D concert. So, yeah, thank you from the bottom of our hearts...
...for supporting us thus far. Please keep supporting us from now on forward. Thank you! Woo!
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Ciao, Tigri! Ciao, ciao, ciao, Just Chats!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice for a whole week, and many more to come!
Yes, this has been a dream come true for me, being in 3D, dancing with you guys. It's so much fun!
So, I really, really appreciate it. Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart.
Big cat hugs! Big Justice!
We're Justice! Woo!
Once again, thank you all for watching our very first 3D collab stream today!
Please keep supporting Justice!
Justice! Just like that! Justice!
Get it? Got it? Done!
Bye-bye, everyone! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Make sure to eat, ignore, hydrate, and all that jazz! Alright, bye!